const examsQuestionStructure = {
    "subjectName": "Science for 8 std",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "question1",
            "answer": "ans1",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question2",
            "answer": "ans2",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question3",
            "answer": "ans3",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question4",
            "answer": "ans4",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question5",
            "answer": "ans1",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question6",
            "answer": "ans2",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question7",
            "answer": "ans3",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question8",
            "answer": "ans4",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question9",
            "answer": "ans1",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question10",
            "answer": "ans2",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        }, {
            "question": "question11",
            "answer": "ans3",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        }, {
            "question": "question12",
            "answer": "ans4",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question13",
            "answer": "ans1",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question14",
            "answer": "ans2",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "question15",
            "answer": "ans3",
            "options": [
                "ans1",
                "ans2",
                "ans3",
                "ans4"
            ]
        }
    ],
    "notes": [
        "10mins exam",
        "start time 10am"
    ]
}

export default examsQuestionStructure